http://www.steelmailbox.com/policies

HOT SALES TOP MAILBOXES, DROP BOXES, LETTER BOXES, COLLECTION BOXES FOR BEST PRICES HomeShop Mailbox10 Gauge Steel MailboxesStainless Steel MailboxesGalvanized Steel MailboxSteel MailboxesAluminum MailboxesHeavy Duty MailboxesLocking MailboxesSecure MailboxesCommercial MailboxesPremium MailboxesMailbox and Post SystemsWall Mount MailboxesDrop BoxesLetter BoxesCollection BoxesLetter LockerFort KnoxManchesterdVaultAllux BoxMailbox PlaquesPosts and SpreadersFAQPoliciesMoreHomeShop Mailbox10 Gauge Steel MailboxesStainless Steel MailboxesGalvanized Steel MailboxSteel MailboxesAluminum MailboxesHeavy Duty MailboxesLocking MailboxesSecure MailboxesCommercial MailboxesPremium MailboxesMailbox and Post SystemsWall Mount MailboxesDrop BoxesLetter BoxesCollection BoxesLetter LockerFort KnoxManchesterdVaultAllux BoxMailbox PlaquesPosts and SpreadersFAQPoliciesHomeShop Mailbox10 Gauge Steel MailboxesStainless Steel MailboxesGalvanized Steel MailboxSteel MailboxesAluminum MailboxesHeavy Duty MailboxesLocking MailboxesSecure MailboxesCommercial MailboxesPremium MailboxesMailbox and Post SystemsWall Mount MailboxesDrop BoxesLetter BoxesCollection BoxesLetter LockerFort KnoxManchesterdVaultAllux BoxMailbox PlaquesPosts and SpreadersFAQPolicies
Our PoliciesPrivacy PolicyWarranty - Items Damaged by ShipperWarranty - Items Damaged by ShipperSteel Mailbox Company LLC. use of personal information that you may submit to Steel Mailbox Company LLC.through this Web site is governed by the Steel Mailbox Company LLC.Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Steel Mailbox Company website.The only personal information we collect is your name, street and email address, telephone number, and credit card information (or if paying by PayByCheck your checking account number).We use the personal information collected from you to answer your questions via phone or email, and to process orders. Such personal information as we collect is not used for any other purpose and is not shared.We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put into place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13 to provide information to us.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request detailing the error(s). To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.Warranty - Items Damaged by ShipperWarranty - Items Damaged by ShipperWarranty - Items Damaged by ShipperAny warranty problems will be handled by the respective manufacturer, although we assist with any warranty claims.    Items damaged by carrier or shipper during delivery are not considered “defective,” but are “damaged by shipper.”  It is the customer’s responsibility to contact us immediately if an item is received in damaged condition, so that we may file a claim with shipper. All packing materials must be kept for claims to be honored in such instances. Please make  detail photo-evidence of defect and contact US immediately.Return & Refund PolicyWarranty - Items Damaged by ShipperReturn & Refund PolicyIf you request refund for order - immediately after placing and automatically  processed  on our website, we process your refund minus your credit card underline Merchant - Processing Fee deduction. Please note, then we are pending your order, the same day, after order is placed - to mailbox Production, and we are unable stop mailbox construction process. Please be sure, you are ordering the correct item, take attention to specific shipping time quotes on our website, different for each unique mailbox.You may return your order for a refund so long as it is in new, resalable condition within thirty (30) days of Primary receipt, under the conditions noted below. All parts, packaging materials, original cartons, and instruction materials must be included. Items such as all CBUs, all Masonry and Column Mailboxes,  all Courier Boxes, all Letter Boxes, all Mail Chests, all Collection Boxes, all Rural Mailboxes, all Letter Boxes, all Mailbox and Post Systems, all Drop Boxes, all Posts, Locking Inserts and Accessories, all Manchester -Qualarc, all Special Lite, all Salsbury, all DVault, all Allux products will incur a 30% Restocking Charge.Please note that  all Custom Fabricated orders including all Letter Locker mailboxes, all Fort Knox mailboxes, all Bulk Orders - e.g. address plaques, all customized Drop Boxes, are non-returnable unless defective. Mailboxes with Custom Addresses installed are not eligible for refund because they are not in new, resalable condition, and cannot be sold as open box item.Custom construct, or modify mailboxes, addressed mailboxes or plaques are therefore non-returnable.When selecting a custom addressed mailbox or address plaque, please avoid typos. Items returned with damage, missing parts or packing materials, or without a Return Merchandise Authorization Number,  are not reliable for refund at the discretion of Steel Mailbox Company LLC.All returns must have a Return Merchandise Authorization Number, so please contact us before returning any item. Please include your Primary receipt - print out of your Invoice which you receive at the time you placed your order online. Refund includes the cost of merchandise minus 30% Restocking Fee and don't include shipping expenses either coming or going unless such merchandise is defective.
Copyright © 2020 Steel Mailbox Company - All Rights ReservedPowered by GoDaddy
